<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Qwixx</string>
    <string name="game_description">Qwixx is a quick-playing dice game in which everyone participates,
        no matter whose turn it is. Each player has a scoresheet with the numbers 2-12 in rows of red
        and yellow and the numbers 12-2 in rows of green and blue.\n\n
    To score points you want to mark off as many numbers as possible, but you can mark off a number only if it\'s to the right
        of all marked-off numbers in the same row.\n\n Players: <b>2-5</b>   Playing Time: <b>15 Min</b>  Age: <b>8+</b>
        \n\n All rights belong to Gamewright @ Application is developed by P. Zhelev
    </string>

    <string name="rules"> QWIXX - RULES\n\n
        The active player throws with all
six dice. The following two actions are now carried out one after the other: first the
first action and only then the second one.\n\n
1.) The active player adds the pips of the two white dice
together and says aloud, and in a clear voice, the sum that
thereby results. Each player may then (but is not obliged
to!) cross out the number that the active player has spoken
out in any colour-row of his choosing.\n\n
    2.) The active player (but not the others!) may then (but
is not obliged to!) add together the pips shown on just
one white dice together with the pips shown on just one
coloured dice of his choosing and cross out the number
corresponding to this sum in the colour-row corresponding
to the colour of the dice chosen. \n\n
        Very important: If the active player crosses out a number neither in the first nor
in the second action, he must make a cross in the column “Misthrows” (Fehlwürfe
je -5). The non-active players do not need to mark a misthrow, regardless of
whether they have chosen to cross out a number or not.\n\n
        FINISHING A ROW \n\n
        If a player wishes to cross out the number at the extreme right end of a colour-row
(red 12, yellow 12, green 2, blue 2) he must first have made at least five crosses
in the colour-row in question. If he makes a cross on the number on the extreme
right, then he should also make a cross on the field directly next to it which shows
a lock symbol. This latter cross will also be counted in the final calculation of total
crosses! This colour-row is now finished and closed off for all the players and no
more crosses can be made in this colour in any of the subsequent rounds. The dice
of the colour corresponding to it is immediately removed from the game and is no
longer needed. \n\n
        The game ends immediately as soon as someone has marked his fourth misthrow.
It also ends immediately as soon as two colour-rows have been completed and
closed off (regardless by which players) and dice of two colours have consequently
been removed from the game.

    </string>

    <color name="orange">#F17117</color>
    <color name="orangePrimaryDark">#d36013</color>
</resources>
